‎NETFLIX アニメシリーズ
‎（フリオの荒い息）
‎（フリオ）ハア ハア…
Feeling a lil' antsy there, Julio?
‎（レベッカ）
‎緊張してるねえ フリオ君
No way!
‎してねえよ！
‎（レベッカ）ワカコに
‎ねじ込まれたって聞いたけどさあ
You're the one Wakako sicced on us, right?
Heard you're David's fan.
‎デイビッドのファンってマジ？
Yeah! But what do you mean
she sicced me on you?
‎（フリオ）マジだよ
‎ねじ込まれたって何だよ！
Hear that, David?
‎（レベッカ）
‎デイビッドのファンねえ
You have fans now.
Probably 'cause you got all swole.
‎有名になってきたじゃん
‎体もでかくなったし
Where's your gun?
‎（デイビッド･マルティネス）
‎銃は？　何を使ってる？
What do you use?
‎はい レキシントンです
Uh, I've got a Lexington.
‎（デイビッド）全然 ダメだな
That won't cut it.
You gonna go up
against Maelstrom with that?
‎こんなもんでメイルストロームの
‎相手をするつもりか？
Use this.
‎これを使え
Seriously, dude?! A fucking Satara!
‎（フリオ）
‎マジっすか サタラじゃないすか！
Nova! Thanks, man!
‎すっげ！　あざっす！
Tech shotguns are so cool.
‎やっぱテック系のショットガン
‎ヤバいっすね
‎（ガチャ！）
Charge-up shots, oh yeah…
‎このチャージが…
‎（チャージ音）
Boom!
‎ドシューン！
‎（チャージ音）
Boom!
‎ドシューン！
‎（チャージ音）
Boom!
Knock it off!
‎（レベッカ）
‎うっぜえ うっぜ うっぜ！
Ow! Stop! Watch the knees!
‎（フリオ）
‎何だよ ヒザ蹴ることねーだろ
‎（レベッカ）ドシュドシュ
‎うっせんだよ　ガキかよ！
What are you, five?!
‎俺の後ろについてろ
‎焦って突っ走るなよ
Just stick behind me. Don't rush ahead.
‎えっ 後ろですか？
You want me to take rear?
I ain't no rookie, man.
‎俺 ルーキーじゃないっすよ
‎（ため息）
Attention, ladies.
‎（ファルコ）
‎お嬢さん方 あと１分で着くぜ
One minute from the destination.
♪～
～♪
‎（ホロ通信：キーウィ）
‎やっぱり相当いるね～
‎タレットも配備されてる
‎ハック用にタグ付けしていくには
‎骨折りそう
‎ここはセオリーどおり
‎正面は避けて裏口 回って
‎（デイビッド）
‎セオリーは無視したいな
‎（レベッカ）‎オーケー
‎（フリオ）
‎あれ？　裏口 探さないの？
‎（レベッカ）
‎あんただけ探してれば？
‎（フリオ）
‎えっ いやいや 俺も行くし
Looks like they're heading in the front.
‎あいつら正面から入ってくぞ
‎（キーウィ）
‎見えてるっての ったく！
Clearly. Meatbrain move!
The fuck?
‎（メイルストローム）
‎ああ？　何だ てめえら！
Who ordered lunch meat?
Ya little babies lost?
‎（メイルストローム）
‎迷子の小ザルちゃんか？
Looks like they wanna start something.
‎（メイルストローム）
‎何 だんまり決め込んでんだ！
You got shit in your ears?!
‎耳にクソでも詰まってんのか？
Better start talking before
I drill you a fresh earhole--
‎そのクソだらけの耳に穴開けたら
‎聞こえるように…
Better stop talking before you die.
‎黙ってないと殺すぞ
‎（一同）オイオイ！
‎（レベッカ）イーハー！
Tagging complete. Short circ incoming…
‎（キーウィ）
‎タグ付け完了　回路ショート
Done! Close-call but made it, asshole!
‎ハア 間に合わせたぞ 早漏野郎
‎（メイルストローム）
‎ぐっ… ネットランナーがいるぞ
Fuck! They've got a netrunner!
‎（発砲音）
‎（レベッカの高笑い）
Ahh! We're all gonna die!
‎ひゃああ！　銃弾の雨だー！
（キーウィ）
数多すぎ　もう無理
Come on!
‎カモ カモ カモ～ン！
Out of ammo!
‎弾切れ～っ！
Bitch got no juice!
‎クソ女 弾切れだぞ！
Fuck her up!
‎ブッ殺せ！
Time for… the big guns!
‎ネクスト～　ビッグガン！
‎（フリオ）タレットガンだ
There's a turret!
‎（ホロ通信：デイビッド）
‎キーウィ
Watch out! The runner's got control of--
‎（メイルストローム）
‎おい ハックされてるぞ ぐわっ！
Damn brat, ordering me around…
‎（キーウィ）
‎あいつ 人使い荒いんだよ
（発砲音）
Ready to play with a real Maelstrom?
‎（メイルストローム）
‎メイルストロームと遊ぼうぜ
Oh, damn…
‎（フリオ）すげえ
That shit even human?!
‎クロームだらけの
‎でかいやつがいるぞ
‎ん？
‎ああ…
‎（メイルストローム）
‎その生身のケツをよお
Gimme that organic ass…
‎（インプラント発動音）
‎ブッ！
‎なっ！
‎（メイルストローム）
‎壊させてくれよー！
And I'll tear you a new hole!
You're the one getting a new hole.
‎頭にケツ穴 増やしてやるよ
‎うおー！　すげー！
‎シュシュシュ ドバーン！
That was insane! …Zoot-zoot-zoot, bang!
Those your new leg implants? Looking good.
シュシュシュ ドバーン
‎新しい強化‎腱(けん)‎ 使ったな
‎いい感じじゃん
‎（キーウィ）‎そいつで最後
‎奥の部屋に人が押し込まれてる
‎救助対象は そこね
‎（デイビッド）‎分かった
Got it! Room in the back, right?
‎（フリオ）分かった 奥の部屋だね
Wait! Julio!
‎（デイビッド）待て フリオ
‎もしトラップがあったら
If there are traps…
‎（爆発音）
‎かーっ
‎（ドアが開く音）
Isabella Morgan, where you at?
‎イザベラ･モーガンはいるか？
‎（ざわめき）
Your dad put out an SOS for you.
‎オヤジさんから保護を頼まれた
You're safe now.
‎もう大丈夫だ
‎（イザベラ）あ…
（泣き声）
‎（ホロコール着信音）
‎（デイビッド）‎ワカコか
‎（ワカコ）
‎イザベラの保護を確認した
‎ようやってくれはった
‎依頼主も泣いて喜ぶやろ
‎（デイビッド）‎そりゃよかった
‎（ワカコ）‎さすが
‎評判どおりのサイバーパンクや
‎（デイビッド）‎新人のことだけど…
‎（ワカコ）
‎ああ すまんかったな
‎あんたと組みたがらはったんやけど
‎とんだ素人やったようやな
‎また何かあったら
‎よろしゅう頼むわ
‎（デイビッド）
‎ああ　よろしく頼むよ
‎（通信切断音）
‎（レベッカのはしゃぐ声）
‎シャシャシャシャ シャ！
‎よっ ほい！
‎アチョーッ！
‎（電子音）
Thank ya kindly.
‎確かに
Thanks for taking the wheel, Falco.
‎いつも助かるよ ファルコ
No sweat off my back.
‎楽に稼がせてもらって悪いな
‎フッ 信頼できるドライバーは
‎貴重だからね
Nah, good drivers are hard to come by.
Dunno about that.
Seems you got a fan club now.
‎今なら お前と組みたいってやつは
‎いくらでもいるだろう
You mean like Julio?
‎フリオみたいに？
‎（ファルコ）
‎あいつは最初に見た時から
I knew that gonk was bluffing
the moment I saw him.
‎やらかしそうだった
‎（デイビッド）ああ
Aren't many veterans who'd work with
a kid like me unless they knew Maine.
‎あんたみたいに
‎メインの知り合いじゃなきゃ
‎若造と組んでくれるベテランは
‎いないからな
Gotta admit, first time you called,
‎（ファルコ）
‎俺だって最初に誘われた時はよ
I thought you were a pushy pipsqueak.
‎ガキのお守りは
‎ごめんだって思ったぜ
‎（２人の笑い声）
But now? Well…
‎（ファルコ）
‎でもまあ 今はこう思ってる
You're gonna go further
than Maine ever could.
‎お前はメインを超えられるやつだ
‎フッ ガラにもねえこと
‎言っちまった
Gonna roll out before this gets all sappy.
Buzz me for your next big gig, huh?
‎また何かあったら呼んでくれ
Catch you later, David. Kiwi.
‎じゃあな デイビッド　キーウィ
See ya.
‎ああ
Bye.
‎（キーウィ）じゃあ
Honestly? I doubted you had it
in you to take the reins.
‎（キーウィ）実際 あんたが
‎ここまで仕切れると思わなかったわ
All thanks to our preem runner.
‎優秀なネットランナーのおかげかな
We both know you don't mean me.
‎（キーウィ）私じゃないでしょ
‎本当に組むべきランナーは
You've asked her, right?
‎声はかけてるんでしょ？
Used to. I kinda gave up trying.
‎（デイビッド）前はね
‎今はもう 誘ってないんだ
Didn't peg her as the type
to get cold feet.
‎（キーウィ）そんなに
‎メンタル弱い子じゃないって——
‎思ってたんだけどな～
I bet it's more than
what happened to Maine and Dorio.
‎（デイビッド）メインとドリオの
‎ことだけじゃないんじゃないかな
Back at the warehouse,
Lucy was acting weird.
‎あの時のルーシー
‎今 思えば様子がおかしかった
Meaning what?
‎（キーウィ）どういうこと？
Whole thing's kind of a blur.
Might've been nothing.
‎いや 俺も その時は
‎普通じゃなかったからさ
Speaking of, you're the one
that brought Lucy into the crew, right?
‎あのさ　もともとルーシーを
‎チームに誘ったのって
‎キーウィなんだよね？
Yeah.
‎（キーウィ）そうよ
She talk to you about her past?
‎昔のことって聞いたことある？
‎（キーウィ）ないわ
Nope.
‎サイバーパンクなんて
Most of the saps in our league
don't bring up the old days.
‎ろくでもない人生だったやつの
‎逃げ道か
Shame, greed,
something to prove… whatever.
‎足元 見えてない夢見野郎の
‎どっちかでしょ？
Whether you're looking for a way out
or a way up, does it matter?
‎過去を詮索するなんて無粋なだけ
‎（デイビッド）ハア…
‎（レベッカ）おいおいおい！
Why the long face, David?!
‎しんきくせーぞ デイビッド
Stop flirting with the nagging hag
and dance with me!
‎オバサンとイチャついてないで
‎踊ろーぜっ フフン
‎（キーウィ）
‎いかにも ろくでもない人生しか
Although some edgerunners die
in more shame than they started with…
‎歩んでなさそうな お子様ね
‎ろくでもねーのは
At least I didn't get flatlined
by a psycho with his dick out in the wind.
‎チンコ丸出しのおっさんに殺された
‎なっさけねえバカアニキだろ
Anyway, have you ever seen
David dance? It's a riot…
‎それよか 知ってる？
‎デイビッドの超ダサい踊り
Sorry, I'm heading out.
Gonna stop by Doc's.
‎（デイビッド）
‎悪い　俺も もう帰るわ
‎ドクんとこ寄る
Wha? Again?
‎（レベッカ）え… えー またー？
Tell him to sell you
a dance chip or something!
‎どうせならダンサー用の
‎インプラント入れろよ
‎（レベッカ）キレッキレのやつ
‎（デイビッド）うるせえよ
-A real good one!
-Shut up.
‎じゃあな
Catch ya later.
Why you gotta play
hard-to-get all the time?!
‎チェッ
‎相変わらず つきあい悪いわ！
‎（キーウィ）アプローチ
‎変えたほうがいいんじゃない？
Why don't you shake up your approach?
Yeah?
‎そうっすかね？
Think I should play shy and nerdy…
at the shy and nerdy?
‎陰キャには陰キャ…
‎とかっすかね…
‎（リパードク）
‎ゆがんだ ぶってえシャフトを
This warped piece of metal's just
shoved up your arm socket.
‎無理やり押し込んでる
‎だけなんだからな
It doesn't fit you in the first place.
‎そもそも体格に合ってねえ
On top of that, it's an old model.
‎モデルも２世代前のモンだし
Got all kinds of next-gen chrome out back…
‎どうだ？　いい軍用の
‎横流し品があるんだ
I'm fine with this one.
‎いいんだ これで
Tsk. Fine. It's your funeral.
‎（リパードク）チッ だったら
‎さっさとイカれちまえよ
Got muscle reinforcers?
Kiroshi's new model?
‎代わりに強化系を頼むよ
‎キロシの最新のある？
Didn't know I was talking to
a tweaked out chromehead.
‎（リパードク）おいおい
‎ホントはとっくに
‎イカれちまってたのか？
I'm not.
‎俺は まともさ
You need to take it easy.
‎（リパードク）しばらくやめとけ
At this rate, ain't no way
your mind can keep up.
‎こんなペースじゃ
‎なじむもんも なじまなくなる
‎（デイビッド）大丈夫さ
I'm fine.
No matter how much chrome I get,
I don't feel a damn thing.
‎どんなインプラントを入れても
‎違和感が全くないんだ
Metal feels better
than being in my own skin.
‎むしろ生身より なじむぐらいだ
Gotta admit, your adaptability to
cyberware is fucking nuts.
‎（リパードク）確かに
‎お前のクロームへの適応性は異常だ
Ain't never seen a kid
cyborg out quite like this.
‎天性の鈍感野郎といっても
‎いいかもしれん
Your cyberware capacity's already--
‎とっくにお前の人間性コストは…
You think you're special?
‎（‎ＪＫ(ジェーケー)‎）‎自分は特別だと？
Just must be special, I guess.
‎（デイビッド）
‎“特別”って言ってほしいね
‎（リパードク）ハッ！
You aiming to be like
Adam Smasher or what?
‎アダム･スマッシャーにでも
‎なろうってのか？
Adam what?
‎（デイビッド）アダム？
Damn. All this time and
you're still a fucking newb.
‎（リパードク）
‎そんだけ名を挙げても
‎まだまだルーキーだな
Don't even know Adam Smasher.
‎アダム･スマッシャーも
‎知らねえとは
Some know him as a war hero
from the 4th Corporate War.
‎やつは第４次企業戦争の時から
To others, a fully cyborged
boogeyman, walking nightmare.
‎一線で生き続けている
‎ほぼ全身クロームのバケモンだ
But to all, a living legend, ask anyone.
‎アダム･スマッシャーは
‎今でも伝説を量産してるって話だ
What kinda legend?
‎（デイビッド）‎伝説を量産？
There's probably a graveyard out there
‎（リパードク）
‎アラサカに歯向かう大物を
full of big shots he flatlined
on Arasaka's orders.
‎墓場送りにしてるってことよ
Sounds like a hoax.
‎ウソくせえ
‎（ホロコール着信音）
‎（デイビッド）ん… キーウィ？
Kiwi?
What's up?
‎（ホロ通信：デイビッド）
‎どうかした？
Can you drop by the Afterlife?
‎（キーウィ）‎あんた
‎アフターライフに今から来られる？
You guys still out bar hopping?
‎（デイビッド）
‎何だよ　飲み足りないのか？
Got someone here who wants to see you.
‎（キーウィ）
‎あんたに会いたいって人がいるの
‎（キーウィ）デイビッド
David.
Hey, Kiwi.
‎やあ キーウィ
Wish you luck.
‎（キーウィ）頑張って
I believe this is the first time
we meet, Mister Martinez.
‎（ファラデー）はじめましてかな？
‎マルティネス君
We've crossed paths…
You came to a party once to talk to Maine.
‎前に一度
‎メインとあんたが会った場にいた
‎（ファラデー）そうか　では改めて
Is that so?
I believe introductions are in order.
I am Faraday.
‎ファラデーだ
You have a job for me?
‎（デイビッド）仕事の話かい？
No need to rush. Let me buy you a drink.
‎（ファラデー）焦らなくていい
‎まずは１杯 おごらせてくれ
I've heard a great deal about you.
‎最近 君の話が
‎よく耳に入ってきてね
You are making quite a name for yourself.
‎かつてない勢いで
‎クレドを稼ぎ続ける——
The rookie with the Sandevistan.
‎サンデヴィスタン使いのルーキー
I've got more than the Sandy now.
‎（デイビッド）サンデヴィスタンは
‎俺の一部でしかない
This is true. It seems now
you are more steel than bone.
‎（ファラデー）確かに
‎今の君は生身のほうが少なそうだ
Maine and I had
a mutually beneficial work relationship.
‎私は よく
‎メインに仕事を頼んでいた
I know.
‎（デイビッド）知ってる
He understood crew chemistry.
‎（ファラデー）
‎彼はチーム戦が得意だった
‎（デイビッド）ああ
He did.
But his flaw was personal attachment.
‎（ファラデー）だが時に
‎仲間同士のなれ合いは集中をそぎ
Familiarity muddies the mind,
leads to ruin.
‎仕事の精度を落とすこともある
I hear that you're also good
with teamwork.
‎君もチーム戦が得意らしいね
But I keep my private
and professional life separate.
‎（デイビッド）
‎そのつもりだし なれ合いもしない
I would like for you to convince me that
you can work at the same level as Maine.
‎（ファラデー）まずは 君が
‎メイン程度の仕事ができるのかを
‎証明してほしい
You're testing me?
‎（デイビッド）テストかい？
You can think of it that way.
‎（ファラデー）
‎そう思ってもらって構わない
You can test me all you want,
but I ain't running jobs for cheap.
‎（デイビッド）テストはいいけど
‎安い仕事はお断りだな
Nothing I do is cheap.
‎（ファラデー）
‎私は 安い仕事はしない
This a Militech job?
‎依頼主はミリテクか？
‎アラサカの商売敵だろ
They're at odds with Arasaka.
As you might expect,
corporate jobs pay out the most.
‎高額報酬の仕事は
‎当然 コーポ案件が多い
Do you oppose?
‎コーポが嫌いかね？
Consider it done.
‎受けよう
Good to hear.
‎（ファラデー）期待している
There is an assignment
I'd like you to take over after this job.
‎これがうまくいったら
‎引き継いでほしい仕事があってね
It's a matter familiar to you.
‎君との因縁もある
You mean the data you wanted from Tanaka?
‎タナカから抜こうとしてた
‎データか？
‎（ファラデー）
‎残念ながらタナカの中に
Unfortunately, I received a report
that Tanaka had no data.
‎データはなかったそうだな
Yup.
‎（デイビッド）ああ
But I also received a report that
you successfully bypassed Arasaka's ICE.
‎（ファラデー）
‎しかしアラサカのセキュリティーは
‎突破したそうじゃないか
And that this wasn't done by Kiwi,
but by a back-up runner.
‎しかもキーウィではなく
‎バックアップのランナーと聞いた
Yeah. Our team's got
lucky with good runners.
‎（デイビッド）
‎ああ うちのチームは
‎ランナーあってこそだ
‎（ファラデー）すばらしい
‎しかし 今は問題がある
Excellent. However, I hear
this runner is not present.
Yeah. They left the team after that case.
‎（デイビッド）ああ　あれ以来
‎チームに合流はしていない
Why is that? Such a waste of good talent.
‎（ファラデー）なぜかね？
‎そんな優秀なランナーなのに
Their heart's just not in it.
‎（デイビッド）
‎本人に その気がなくてね
It wouldn't hurt to try
to convince her again.
‎君が説得すれば戻るかもしれない
Easier said than done…
‎そうシンプルじゃ… あ…
‎アラサカも もうミリテクに
‎狙われてることに気付いてんだろ？
Arasaka knows that
Militech's after them, right?
Of course.
‎（ファラデー）
‎もちろん そうだろう
What's Militech after
that they'd want this bad?
‎ミリテクが そうまでして
‎欲しがるものって何なんだ？
That is my concern and none of yours.
‎知る必要はないし
‎知らないほうがうまくいく
Needless details
would only get in your way.
‎余計な情報は邪魔なだけだ
Learn anything new that might help?
‎新しい情報があるのか？
Not yet. But as they say,
"Good things come to those who wait."
‎今は まだない
‎だがチャンスは必ず来る
But you've yet to prove
that you're worth my time.
‎その前に力を示せ
You're home.
‎（ルーシー）おかえり
It's pretty late.
‎（ルーシー）遅かったね
Got caught up.
‎（デイビッド）
‎もっと早く帰るつもりだった
Made a victory lap at Minjung's?
‎（ルーシー）
‎ミンジョンの店に寄ったんでしょ？
Yeah.
‎（デイビッド）ああ
‎（ルーシー）仕事は無事に？
Any problems on the job?
We lost someone tonight.
‎（デイビッド）仲間が１人やられた
‎（ルーシー）誰？
Who?
Greenhorn solo Wakako sent us.
‎（デイビッド）
‎ワカコからつけられた飛び入り
Oh. But everything went fine otherwise?
‎（ルーシー）なんだ…
‎依頼は うまくいったんでしょ？
Easy. The newb just jumped the gun.
‎（デイビッド）上々
‎ただ そいつがトチっただけ
‎（ルーシー）
‎ちょっと前の自分を重ねたりした？
Sounds like some other newb I once knew.
‎（デイビッド）うるさい
Hey.
‎（ルーシーの笑い声）
So…
‎ねえ
‎んー？
We got something big coming up.
‎でかい仕事が入りそうなんだ
How fun.
‎あら すてき
And it'd really help
if you'd get on board…
‎でさ できれば その…
‎ルーシーも
Two runners makes for a crowd, doesn't it?
‎今のチームに
‎ランナー２人も要らないでしょ？
‎そんなこと… 俺は君のほうが
You know that I'd rather have--
‎ねえ デイビッド
David, please.
‎もう少しだけ待って
I need more time.
Fine. Okay.
‎ああ 分かった
‎（デイビッド）今日も潜ってたの？
‎（ルーシー）うん
You were diving again?
Why don't you buy a runnersuit?
‎（デイビッド）
‎いいランナースーツ 買ったら？
Don't need one.
‎（ルーシー）要らないわ
We can get you a new chair.
The ice-bath can't be comfortable.
‎（デイビッド）
‎最新のチェアも買おう
‎氷風呂なんかより
‎ずっといいだろ？
Thank you.
But I don't like wearing a suit.
‎（ルーシー）ありがと
‎でもスーツは好きじゃないの
‎そっか　知らなくてごめん
Oh.
Sorry, I didn't know.
‎プハッ
Hey, David?
‎（ルーシー）ねえ デイビッド
‎ん？
Come with me.
‎来て
‎え？
Whoa! Look at the stars!
‎（デイビッド）
‎おおっ　すっげえ星！
‎（ルーシー）ナイトシティじゃ
‎絶対 見れないでしょ？
Can't get a view like this in the city.
‎（デイビッド）
‎ハハッ つかめるかな？
-Think I can catch one?
-As if.
‎（ルーシー）バーカ
Wish we could've seen the moon.
‎月も見たかったな～
The stars shine brighter
because the moon's not out.
‎月がないから
‎星がきれいに見えるのよ
Really?
‎そうなの？
The moon outshines the stars.
‎月の明るさは星を隠してしまう
‎アカデミーで何 習ってたわけ？
What were they teaching you
at the Academy?
I'm a drop-out, remember?
‎退学してっし
Right, right.
‎そうでした
‎俺 ナイトシティから出るの
‎初めてだ
Never been outside of the city.
‎そっか
Huh.
You had a life outside the city once, huh?
‎（デイビッド）君は
‎ナイトシティだけじゃないんだね
The city looks like a cage
made of lights from here.
‎（ルーシー）
‎ここから見るナイトシティは
‎まるで光の牢獄
You may not remember…
‎（デイビッド）前にさ…
‎（ルーシー）うん
You said you and I are different.
‎（デイビッド）
‎君と俺は違うって言ったよね？
Yes.
‎（ルーシー）うん
‎（デイビッド）あれ どういう意味
What did you mean by that?
Don't wanna talk about it?
‎言いたくない？
You'd rather not hear.
‎（ルーシー）聞きたい？
‎（デイビッド）君のこと
‎もっと知りたいと思ってる
I just… wanna know more about you.
‎（深呼吸）
‎（ルーシー）‎アラサカ
‎（デイビッド）‎アラサカ？
Arasaka.
Arasaka?
‎（ルーシー）‎そうよ　子供の頃
‎私は別の国のアラサカの施設にいた
Yes.
I was born in a different country
and raised in an Arasaka facility.
Including me, 13 children passed
proficiency tests to become netrunners.
‎私も入れて 施設には
‎ランナーの適性テストを通過した
‎13人の子供たち
Kids who wouldn't be missed
if they disappeared.
‎身寄りのない者ばかりだった
"We'll serve the world's most
powerful megacorp one day…"
‎世界一の企業の
‎ネットランナーになれるんだ
‎そんな期待があったから
That dream is what got us through
the hard days of training.
‎厳しい訓練にも
‎耐えられたのかもしれない
‎私たちは選んでもない夢を
‎自然と追いかけていた
It's the dream we were given,
the dream we never questioned.
But when training ended,
we weren't assigned to a corpo office.
‎訓練を終えた私たちが
‎連れていかれたのは
‎コーポのオフィスなんかじゃ
‎なかった
We were taken to an underground facility
where we were constantly forced to dive…
‎暗い地下の施設
‎そこで強制的にダイブさせられた
They sent us into the Old Net.
‎私たちが向かったのは
‎オールドネットだった
Old Net?
‎オールドネットって 確か
That's the old internet domain that
collapsed around 50 years ago, right?
‎半世紀ぐらい前に崩壊した
‎古いネット領域だろ？
Yes.
‎そう　史上最高のランナーで
‎デーモンの生みの親
Brought down by history's greatest
netrunner, creator of daemons…
‎ハッキングの始祖
Hacker savant, legend, Rache Bartmoss.
‎レジェンド
‎レーシィー･バートモス
The guy that brought down
78 percent of the world wide web.
‎（デイビッド）
‎ワールドネットの78％を崩壊させた
‎伝説の指名手配犯…
‎（ルーシー）
‎彼のデータクラッシュウイルスは
His DataKrash virus shattered cyberspace…
‎サイバー空間を断絶させ
…Broke the Net into a scattered
mosaic of isolated localnets.
‎ネットを限定的な枠組みでしか
‎アクセスできない——
‎とても‎矮小(わいしょう)‎なローカルネットへ
‎追いやった
‎アラサカの目的は
Arasaka's purpose was in the Old Net.
The legacies of the past.
‎オールドネットに隔離された
‎過去の遺産
Vast amounts of lost knowledge.
‎膨大な知識と情報
And we were soldiers being sent to a nest
of illegal malware and aggressive AI.
‎私たちは
‎違法なマルウェアと不良ＡＩの巣へ
‎送られる兵隊だった
Advanced netrunners can dive
into it with their whole mind.
‎高度なネットランナーは
‎そこへ精神ごとダイブできる
‎（デイビッド）‎ディープダイブ
You mean deep-diving.
And diving materializes cyberspace
into a traversable world.
‎（ルーシー）‎ダイブによって
‎可視化されるサイバー空間
But whenever we uncovered
any rare data cache…
‎そのオールドネットの中で
‎レアデータを見つけると…
‎（ルーシー）えっ？
Rogue AIs would find and attack us.
‎（ルーシー）‎凶暴なＡＩが
‎私たちを見つけ 襲いかかってきた
We were picked off one by one.
‎オールドネットから
‎帰れない子たちが続いた
I continued to dive,
thinking that each time would be my last.
‎次は私の番かもしれない
‎そう思いながら潜った
‎すぐに私たちは
‎片手で数えられるようになった
Soon, there were only
a handful of us left.
We were being killed
to live someone else's dream.
‎他人から与えられた夢は
‎やっぱりろくなもんじゃなかった
So we thought, "If we're going to die,
why not die trying to escape?"
‎だから どうせ死ぬなら
‎みんなで脱走しようって決めた
（警報音）
The tech staff didn't stand a chance.
Not against the skills they'd taught us.
（警報音）
‎私たちは 育てられた力で
‎大人たちを殺して——
And we escaped.
‎逃げた
‎（子供たちの荒い息）
‎（銃声）
‎（女の子の悲鳴）
‎（男の子の悲鳴）
‎（ルーシー）‎とにかく走った
I kept running.
（銃声）
‎（ルーシー）‎とにかく走った
I could hear my friends crying out,
（銃声）
‎誰かが泣き叫ぶ声が聞こえたけど
‎振り返らなかった
but I didn't look back.
‎（ルーシー）あ… ああ…
‎（ルーシー）
‎気付いたら ゴミの中で生きてた
When I came to,
I was living out in a junkyard.
After that, I was too scared
to stay in one place.
‎それからは
‎１つの場所にいるのが怖くて
So I traveled to different cities.
‎いろんなとこへ行った
But there's no place like Night City
if all you wanna do is hide.
‎ナイトシティは
‎隠れるには本当にいい所
You still feel like you're being chased?
‎（デイビッド）
‎今でも追われてる感じがするの？
‎そうでもないかな
Not really. Guess I just got
too comfortable here.
‎ナイトシティの居心地がよすぎて
‎恐怖心がマヒしちゃったのかもね
Or maybe I've grown used to being scared.
‎ん…　あっ
‎（ルーシー）その手…
That hand…
It's nothing.
It'll be alright in a second.
‎大丈夫　すぐ治まるから
You haven't changed at all.
Still living for someone else's dream.
‎変わらないね
‎また‎他人(ひと)‎の夢を背負って生きてる
‎あ…
It's not like I don't understand.
‎（ルーシー）気持ちは分かるけどさ
‎（デイビッド）うん
I don't think I'm scared
for myself anymore.
‎たぶん 私は今はもう
‎自分のことでは怖がらない
I'm more scared that…
‎今 怖いのは あなたが…
Someday, you'll…
‎フッ
‎あ…
‎（ホロ通信：ジェイミー）
‎ええ　ほとんどのデータが
Yes. I was able to recover
most of the data.
‎復旧できました
The information on
one of the test subjects
‎しかし 例のプロダクトの
‎被験者データの中で
appears to be completely corrupted.
‎損傷が激しいものがありまして
‎それがいまだ…
I would say that it was
intentionally manipulated.
‎意図的に破壊された
‎可能性があります
There's no trace on the ICE.
‎ＩＣＥ(アイス)‎に痕跡もない
This hacking couldn't have been done
by an average runner.
‎スゴ腕のネットランナーの関与は
‎間違いありません
I don't believe Tanaka
would have erased it.
‎タナカが消去する理由もないので
So it must have been manipulated
during his capture.
‎拉致された時に
‎破壊されたと思うのが自然でしょう
Understood.
I'll see what I can do to restore it.
‎はい　バックアップからの
‎復元を試みます
（足音）
Goodbye.
‎では
‎（ノイズ音）
‎（ジェイミー）ぐうっ！
‎ぐううっ…
‎クッ！
‎があああーっ！
♪～
～♪